Thank you for watching!
Nogisaka's Daytime
Hello, this is Pararama, the official Nogisaka's daytime meeting, and I'm looking forward to working with you.
I am Pararama, a member of Nogisaka's official board.
Please welcome Nogisaka!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on...
Coming Soon! Coming Soon!
Let's hear it for today's project. Let's go! 35 single hits!
Oh!
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
And now, on the 10th of April, we'll be releasing our 35th single...
Gyaos Night.
No, no, no.
He was a good pitcher for our generation for a long time, wasn't he?
Is that Gyaos Naito's song?
Not at all.
Have you lost your mind, Mr. Akimoto?
Gyaos Naito?
Equal opportunity.
Yes, sir.
Not even close.
When I said it, everyone was on the edge of their seats.
They were like, "What are you talking about?
I wondered, too.
Yamashita's graduation will be centered on a single, right?
That's right.
I heard you've been doing this all by yourself.
Yes, I went it alone this time.
Not all of you, just Yamashita?
The 35th single, "Pitta Kina"?
Yes, I came to Osaka this time.
Osaka?
Yamashita, who will graduate in May, is the center of the group, and he's going to pray for a hit this time.
Manako did it in her car, didn't she?
That way?
That's what she said.
I wanted to do something on an unexpected level.
Yamashita's challenge is to do something on an unexpected level.
Ueno Chikara reports
Circus!
The Kinoshita Dance Circus boasts 122 years of history, and the trapeze is the highlight of the show.
Yamashita challenged to perform the trapeze with one successful shot!
The audience is watching the trapeze artist jump out of the 13-meter-high platform with only one chance to perform.
Yamashita Dai Cirque's hit project to challenge the success of the trapeze is the last one, and it's also the last time I'm going to pray for a hit.
I'll do my best for the last time in Nogichu, too.
Yamashita Circus is full of uncertainty. I asked him about the chances of success.
The chances of success are about 2 out of every 50 people who try.
That's not easy!
There hasn't been a woman who has succeeded in the past few decades.
We've faced many challenges in the past, but this time, we're going to try the most difficult challenge in our history.
This is by far the most difficult challenge in the history of the project.
This time, Yamashita will be attempting what is known as a "hand jump.
He jumps out of a platform 13 meters above the ground with good timing and jumps in the air.
Jumping in the air
Jump in the air
If the person on the other side catches you, you succeed!
You start by practicing jumping out of the air with a 6 kg bar on the ground.
So you go out from this state.
This is the most important part.
Timing.
There's a wire attached to the bar, and if it slacks off...
If it slackens and falls, the hand that's holding this bar will be torn off.
Torn?
Not torn?
The skin of my hand is... falling off like this.
It's all sticky.
Our hands have about 5 or 6 layers like this.
If we practice too long, they'll turn this way.
We can't practice too long.
Our hands won't be able to hold it.
That's right.
We need to conserve our strength for the show, so we'll practice in short bursts.
I see.
You can't practice that much?
Oh, that's right.
That's good.
No, that's why I'm scared.
Two threes.
Ouch.
Scary.
This is the most important one, so I practice it the most.
The margin of error is only about 0.2 seconds.
Then you can't have it a little scary.
I'm scared.
Even the slightest mistake is not allowed.
That's right... you can't get the timing right if you do it all the time.
Then we move on to the key to success, the posture in the air and the jump.
Timing your feet from here.
That's great!
Roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll, roll
This is so hard!
I'm not going up very high!
It's going to get bigger and bigger like that.
That's how big my fingers are in the real thing.
Scary, scary!
I'm actually going to fly from here.
Yes, sir.
It's pretty big.
Wow.
Oh, no.
You know what? I'm gonna lose it.
Yes, sir.
I'm scared.
First of all, how does it feel to be dangling?
My hands are killing me.
I think I'll swing this time.
Here we go!
Come on!
I'm gonna let go.
Oh, my God!
I'm so scared.
This is so hard.
Hang in there, hang in there, hang in there.
I'm at the end of my rope.
I'll get off in front of you.
I'll get down in front of you.
Oh, no!
I have no muscle strength at all.
It's a one-shot deal. If you can get through the first swing...
And then... when you get to this point, you have to let go of the hand.
I don't know how to let go.
I'll get over it the first time.
I understand.
I'm in a position where I have to carry all the pressure.
I have to carry all the pressure, so I have to be in the air and everything.
I had a stomach ache for about 3 or 4 days before.
But I'm doing it, I'm doing it.
Don't you feel like your hands are about to come apart, like at first?
Yes, I'm getting used to it.
Yamashita is gradually getting used to it, but there is a big concern about the trapeze.
You're so good at this!
It's so high!
I'm really not good at screaming.
I hate bungees the most.
Bungy and sky-diving are my least favorite, because I don't want to be punished or have to play hardball.
I've always avoided bungees and skydiving.
I've been avoiding bungees and skydiving because they're the two things I'm most afraid of.
Yamashita says he is not very good at heights.
I've never seen anything like this.
Yamashita says he is not good at heights.
I climbed up to this 2m high practice step.
No, it's scary even at 2m
No, I'm scared.
Dangerous!
Scary.
It's 6km
That's 6km, isn't it?
I'm scared
Scary.
It's almost 3 meters high
It's almost 3 meters high!
Even at this height, I can't get my feet under me
I can't even look down
I know I'm the last one
I want to give it my all
I really want to give it my all and take on the challenge properly.
I'll jump next time.
Yes, sir.
Wow, wow, wow!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Oh, that's good.
That's about right.
That's great!
I was here before, and now I'm here.
Progress here.
This progress is amazing.
That's great.
I'm getting really good shape from what we've practiced.
This is today.
Today?
I have a little bit of hope.
From what I've seen so far in practice... of all the women I've tried...
I feel like you have a great sense of style.
That's good.
So get through the first one.
If you can get past the middle.
If you can get past the middle and get your hands off, the possibilities are endless.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
I'm sure you'll get the doctor's blessing.
After this, we'll do it for real.
All Yamashita can do is climb down from a platform 1/100th the height of the real thing.
Seriously, he'll never experience that height.
I've never seen it before.
You've never practiced catching a ball.
You don't know how it's going to go.
We haven't.
I'm telling you the truth.
I've never experienced the fear of jumping out of a stage and being 13 meters high.
Kinoshita Grand Circus opens the show.
Yamashita participates in the air-conditioned trapeze show.
The best part of the circus, the big show.
Almost a full house of 1,500 spectators entered
The stage was filled with excitement.
And 10 minutes to go until Yamashita's performance
Final start of construction in the back of the store
Good morning!
Yamashita is on final standby as his performance is just around the corner.
I'm amazed you guys cooperated on this.
I'm Mizuki Yamashita.
Here are some of Mizuki Yamashita's favorite snacks.
The audience of 1,500 people is watching the show.
Finally, the aerial planko show is about to begin!
She's showing us what it's like to be on stage.
There's always something going on.
Amazing.
All right, I'm out of the air.
Great experience.
Today, we have a person who is going to try aerial black
Today's challengers are Yamashita and Mizuta from the riding and small arms rooms!
Here's a big round of applause for Mr. Hanyu.
Yes, welcome!
Yamashita jumped out onto the stage, but after that, the first kan-ron was heard.
Can I go up there by myself?
It's my first time, too. I'm really not good at it.
I'm really not good at it.
I really can't.
Yes, you have to use a ladder to climb up to the 13-meter height right away!
I fought off my fear, climbed the ladder, and reached the 13-meter trapeze launching pad for the first time.
And here the trapeze show begins!
All the spectators are smiling and enjoying the show.
The fear of heights and the nervousness of fear made the audience's eyes bulging with fear as they went into the trapeze.
And just when the show was at its most exciting, it was time for Yamashita the Great Circus to take the stage.
And they succeeded!
Here comes today's challenger!
Mizuki Yamashita from Dojizaka 46!
I think she's nervous, too.
Amazing.
A one-shot competition?
Please give a big round of applause!
I hope you're not too excited.
I'm so happy!
Yamashita, the idol with a big heart and a big smile on his face.
But the first time I saw the scenery 13 meters above the ground and the fear of riding on the unstable 15-centimeter square platform...
I can't stop shaking.
Go for it!
Go! Go for it!
That's great! They're cheering for us.
Go, go, go!
Let's go! They're coming!
They're coming! They're here!
Oh, man, this is crazy. It's the last one.
I'm going to give it my all.
I really want to give it my all and take on this challenge properly.
Dai Yamashita, the culmination of his 8 years with Nogizaka46
A serious challenge to give it all he's got
Will the trapeze for a hit succeed?
This is Mizuki Yamashita's challenge!
Please do it!
It's just me. I'm nervous.
Go for it!
What are you doing?
I lost my hand.
Yamashita fell before jumping in the air
His arms couldn't handle the acceleration of the jump.
She let go of the bar, and it was impossible to jump.
Mizuki Yamashita.
Thank you very much!
Yamashita greeted the audience with a smile, and ended the show with a disappointment.
Huh?
Huh? She's crying!
I'm scared.
I was scared and frustrated.
Fear of heights I had never experienced in my life.
I had no time at all to take advantage of the timing I'd learned in practice.
Thank you for watching
Yamashita says he let go of his hand
Although he was overcome with fear at the start of the race
out of a sense of responsibility as a center
I managed to take that step.
From fear and frustration
Yamashita is no longer able to comment
Unfortunately, the prayer for a hit ended here
but Yamashita came back again.
Yamashita came back again
We can't end things like this.
He volunteered to do it again.
After the performance
There was no audience, but he was allowed to fly one more time.
I didn't want to go home feeling bad about it.
I don't think success is everything.
Even if I failed, he said it's great to be out in front of the audience.
He said it was great that I was able to come out ahead.
I want to cherish the fact that I took on the challenge.
I lost my head and let go of my hand once in the black in the air.
I thought I'd never be able to stand in the same place again.
I don't want it to end like this.
I want to be able to say that I gave it my all, no matter what the situation.
The history of the single hit prayer, in which we have challenged many impossible tasks up to now
The members have shown us not only their successes, but also their limits.
but also their own limits.
They're going to challenge one more time, so please accept my best regards.
And the members of the circus
Yamashita, who has made up his mind
Facing himself
To overcome the strong steps
to overcome the strong steps.
I did it. I'll be fine.
What should I do?
You're still shaking.
No, I'm scared.
I can see more down there than I did on the first try.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm scared.
I'm going to let go...
Oh, my God.
I'm scared.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
Let's go down slowly.
That's right.
It never gets any scarier.
I'm even more scared now.
I can go because I have a client and he's going at that speed.
Fear takes over again, and I can't stop crying.
If I can't do it anymore, let's just stop.
Go for it!
Yamashita, you've done it!
I still can't jump out again, can I?
Go!
I'm ready.
Yes!
Facing the height that once knocked him down
Yamashita still chooses to take on the challenge
I'm scared, I'm scared
Let's go with the flow
Go for it!
Yes, please do
Go for once!
Mizuki Yamashita of Nogizaka46 wants to be the one who challenges himself to the utmost
With this belief in mind, she jumped for the second time.
What will be the result?
Don't let go of my hand!
Go!
Here I go!
Let's go up!
Et cetera, et cetera, et cetera.
All right, all right, all right.
Don't let him do it!
Now Yamashita grabs the bar and jumps out.
He's got a good airborne position.
If he released his hand at the right moment, he could have succeeded.
But he missed.
Yeah, but it came out well. Now that wasn't awesome.
It died.
Ah, another night's out.
Tears of frustration. Scared.
Scared.
Again no words,
Tears spilling down.
But,
Yamashita faced his fear and made two attempts. Although he did not reach success,
he showed us that he would not run away from the biggest obstacle in his life, but would fight it.
I see.
I didn't succeed, but I took on the challenge. I could not succeed.
That's rare, Yamashita cries so much these days.
I myself am so bad at roller coasters that I would never ride them by myself,
But it was about eight times scarier.
That height is scary, isn't it?
But the people at the circus were really kind and let me try a second time,
I was really surprised. I was really surprised that they were doing such a great job.
Kaede Sado, how do you like it?
The courage to do it in front of the audience at that height was just amazing.
I have never seen so many people so weak in front of a mountain,
He must have really faced a great deal of fear.
Right, Sakaguchi?
But, Yamashita, you did a great job.
That's when I started thinking about it.
But it's frustrating.
It's frustrating, because I haven't been able to do anything else.
What?
I'll do it again.
You don't have much time before graduation.
That's fine.
I think we should just go for it.
I did.
You don't mean you're just going blank, do you?
Yes, I'll make it up as I go along.
I'll digest it in some way.
Taking such feelings of Yamashita into consideration, we decided to go on a location that will lead to the future of Nogizaka.
What is it about?
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching!
get down
If you are alone, dance!
get down get down
Raleigh Night for a reason
You must have made up your mind
There's nothing to be nervous about
Get down get down
jump into the group
yeah
Your body's in sync with the rest of your body
Step by step
A new one is just around the corner
The instinct to love The experience of grace
Is your ticket to the future
coming soon
You and I both have an equal chance
All you have to do is believe in yourself and just sit back and wait
You and I both have a chance to come soon
There's no point in comparing yourself with others
Nanana...
You'll hear it.
Footsteps approaching
NaNaNaNaNaNaNaNaNa
Be happy
NaNaNaNaNaNaNaNa
Get down Get down Put your hands up Start your party
Get down Get down Be yourself
Get down Get down Get your groove on Step the E to E
Get down Get down 1,2,3 Get into it
You and I both get equal chances If you believe in yourself, you'll just have to wait and see
You and me, we both get our chance, it doesn't matter if we compare ourselves to those around us.
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
The sound of footsteps approaching
na na na na na na na
Be happy na na na na na na
na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
It's just like you were there.
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na.
A view of the future.
Na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na na
It's your turn now
Na Na Na Na Na Na Na Na
I dance, you dance
I dance, I dance, you dance
Who doesn't like high music?
Okay, we'll go with this group.
I just brought it down so fast, it's already coming off.
Let's try it again a little higher.
No, no, no, it's already taken.
The 35th single, Shadow River, Natsuzakura's music video is now on view!
Mobile selection for Under Live starts today!
Yamashita's last campaign is
Thanks to Nogizaka and for the future
Yamashita's last campaign was to thank Nogizaka and for the future of Nogizaka
How did it end?
This is Inoue Naki.
I ate tteokbokki this morning and it made me swell up!
Please subscribe to my channel!